var game1 = [
    {
        number: 1,
        question: "pick a letter",
        answer1: "a",
        answer1color: "#f5f5f5",
        answer2: "b",
        answer2color: "#f5f5f5",
        answer3: "c",
        answer3color: "#f5f5f5",
        answer4: "d",
        answer4color: "#f5f5f5",
        correctAnswer: 1,
        correctMessage: "very good",
        incorrectMessage: "incorrect - a letter is a",
        backgroundColor: "#f5f5f5",
        fontColor: "#333333",
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        question: "turn a letter to a color",
        answer1: "b88181",
        answer1color: "#B88181",
        answer2: "777777",
        answer2color: "#777777",
        answer3: "aaaaaa",
        answer3color: "#aaaaaa",
        answer4: "f6adad",
        answer4color: "#F6ADAD",
        correctAnswer: 3,
        correctMessage: "nicely done",
        incorrectMessage: "sadly no. letters can be used for colors - so a letter in a color is aaaaaa",
        backgroundColor: "#aaaaaa",
        fontColor: "#333333",
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        question: "pick 1 number",
        answer1: "4",
        answer1color: "#d3d3d3",
        answer2: "3",
        answer2color: "#d3d3d3",
        answer3: "2",
        answer3color: "#d3d3d3",
        answer4: "1",
        answer4color: "#d3d3d3",
        correctAnswer: 4,
        correctMessage: "correct",
        incorrectMessage: "incorrect - 1 number is 1",
        backgroundColor: "#d3d3d3",
        fontColor: "#ffffff",
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        question: "turn 1 number to 1 color",
        answer1: "aaaaaa",
        answer1color: "#AAAAAA",
        answer2: "5d5d5d",
        answer2color: "#5D5D5D",
        answer3: "332424",
        answer3color: "#332424",
        answer4: "111111",
        answer4color: "#111111",
        correctAnswer: 4,
        correctMessage: "you are correct",
        incorrectMessage: "sadly no. numbers can also be used for colors - so 1 number as a color is 111111",
        backgroundColor: "#111111",
        fontColor: "#ffffff",
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        question: "combine a letter with 1 number",
        answer1: "eda6a6",
        answer1color: "#EDA6A6",
        answer2: "a1a1a1",
        answer2color: "#a1a1a1",
        answer3: "b17c7c",
        answer3color: "#B17C7C",
        answer4: "ededed",
        answer4color: "#ededed",
        correctAnswer: 2,
        correctMessage: "you are correct",
        incorrectMessage: "that is incorrect - we combined a with 1 to get a1a1a1",
        backgroundColor: "#a1a1a1",
        fontColor: "#ffffff",
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        question: "now flip it",
        answer1: "1a1a1a",
        answer1color: "#1A1A1A",
        answer2: "664848",
        answer2color: "#664848",
        answer3: "666666",
        answer3color: "#666666",
        answer4: "b3b3b3",
        answer4color: "#B3B3B3",
        correctAnswer: 1,
        correctMessage: "nicely done",
        incorrectMessage: "unfortunately no - flipping a1a1a1 gets 1a1a1a",
        backgroundColor: "#1a1a1a",
        fontColor: "#ffffff",
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        question: "now convert it",
        answer1: "26, 26, 26",
        answer1color: "rgb(26, 26, 26)",
        answer2: "102, 72, 72",
        answer2color: "rgb(102, 72, 72)",
        answer3: "102, 102, 102",
        answer3color: "rgb(102, 102, 102)",
        answer4: "179, 179, 179",
        answer4color: "rgb(179, 179, 179)",
        correctAnswer: 1,
        correctMessage: "you are following along nicely",
        incorrectMessage: "sadly no - converting 1a1a1a to rgb would be (26, 26, 26)",
        backgroundColor: "rgb(26, 26, 26)",
        fontColor: "#ffffff",
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        question: "quadruple the ends",
        answer1: "180, 45, 180",
        answer1color: "rgb(180, 45, 180)",
        answer2: "129, 71, 129",
        answer2color: "rgb(129, 71, 129)",
        answer3: "180, 99, 180",
        answer3color: "rgb(180, 99, 180)",
        answer4: "104, 26, 104",
        answer4color: "rgb(104, 26, 104)",
        correctAnswer: 4,
        correctMessage: "well done",
        incorrectMessage: "that is incorrect - we multiply both ends by 4 to get (108, 26, 108)",
        backgroundColor: "rgb(104, 26, 104)",
        fontColor: "#ffffff",
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        question: "eliminate the center",
        answer1: "104, 0, 104",
        answer1color: "rgb(104, 0, 104)",
        answer2: "180, 54, 180",
        answer2color: "rgb(180, 54, 180)",
        answer3: "129, 39, 129",
        answer3color: "rgb(129, 39, 129)",
        answer4: "180, 0, 180",
        answer4color: "rgb(180, 0, 180)",
        correctAnswer: 1,
        correctMessage: "you are correct",
        incorrectMessage: "incorrect - we zeroed out the center to get (104, 0, 104)",
        backgroundColor: "rgb(104, 0, 104)",
        fontColor: "#ffffff",
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        question: "cut the tail",
        answer1: "180, 0, 0",
        answer1color: "rgb(180, 0, 0)",
        answer2: "129, 39, 39",
        answer2color: "rgb(129, 39, 39)",
        answer3: "104, 0, 0",
        answer3color: "rgb(104, 0, 0)",
        answer4: "180, 54, 54",
        answer4color: "rgb(180, 54, 54)",
        correctAnswer: 3,
        correctMessage: "nicely done",
        incorrectMessage: "sadly no - we zeroed out the last number to get (104, 0, 0)",
        backgroundColor: "rgb(104, 0, 0)",
        fontColor: "#ffffff",
    },
    {
        number: 11,
        question: "flip it",
        answer1: "55, 55, 180",
        answer1color: "rgb(55, 55, 180)",
        answer2: "0, 0, 104",
        answer2color: "rgb(0, 0, 104)",
        answer3: "39, 39, 129",
        answer3color: "rgb(39, 39, 129)",
        answer4: "0, 0, 180",
        answer4color: "rgb(0, 0, 180)",
        correctAnswer: 2,
        correctMessage: "well done",
        incorrectMessage: "unfortunately no - to flip it we switch the first and last number to get (0, 0, 104)",
        backgroundColor: "rgb(0, 0, 104)",
        fontColor: "#ffffff",
    },
    {
        number: 12,
        question: "double everything",
        answer1: "0, 0, 80",
        answer1color: "rgb(0, 0, 80)",
        answer2: "65, 65, 216",
        answer2color: "rgb(65, 65, 216)",
        answer3: "0, 0, 157",
        answer3color: "rgb(0, 0, 157)",
        answer4: "0, 0, 208",
        answer4color: "rgb(0, 0, 208)",
        correctAnswer: 4,
        correctMessage: "you are doing well",
        incorrectMessage: "incorrect - doubling (0, 0, 104) gets us to (0, 0, 208)",
        backgroundColor: "rgb(0, 0, 208)",
        fontColor: "#ffffff",
    },
    {
        number: 13,
        question: "flip it again",
        answer1: "208, 0, 0",
        answer1color: "rgb(208, 0, 0)",
        answer2: "157, 0, 0",
        answer2color: "rgb(157, 0, 0)",
        answer3: "216, 65, 65",
        answer3color: "rgb(216, 65, 65)",
        answer4: "80, 0, 0",
        answer4color: "rgb(80, 0, 0)",
        correctAnswer: 1,
        correctMessage: "nice work",
        incorrectMessage: "unfortunately no - to flip it we switch the first and last number to get (208, 0, 0)",
        backgroundColor: "rgb(208, 0, 0)",
        fontColor: "#222222",
    },
    {
        number: 14,
        question: "convert it back",
        answer1: "d00000",
        answer1color: "#D00000",
        answer2: "9d0000",
        answer2color: "#9D0000",
        answer3: "d84141",
        answer3color: "#D84141",
        answer4: "5000000",
        answer4color: "#500000",
        correctAnswer: 1,
        correctMessage: "well done",
        incorrectMessage: "incorrect - we can convert back to a hex code to get d00000",
        backgroundColor: "#D00000",
        fontColor: "#ffffff",
    },
    {
        number: 15,
        question: "zero out the letters and...",
        answer1: "999999",
        answer1color: "#999999",
        answer2: "4d4d4d",
        answer2color: "#4D4D4D",
        answer3: "4d3636",
        answer3color: "#4D3636",
        answer4: "000000",
        answer4color: "#000000",
        correctAnswer: 4,
        correctMessage: "",
        incorrectMessage: "",
        backgroundColor: "#000000",
        fontColor: "#ffffff",
    },
]